y2mate.info 2019-12-21

# Y2Mate│Privacy Policy

Last updated on August 18, 2018

Y2Mate is dedicated to protecting your privacy. Please expressly read the Privacy Statement below and also any supplemental information listed to the right for additional details about particular sites and services that you may use.

It does not apply to those Y2Mate supported sites, services and products that do not display or link to this statement or that have their own privacy statements. If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us.

1\. Logging IP Addresses

Our different processes do not require to know your IP so we do not know and do not collect any IP addresses.

2\. Third Party Applications

We store all data that you transmit to us during a registering/ordering/purchasing process (even when the transaction is canceled) and also when you subscribe to our services and/or wish to use our services. If you register to use our services online, purchase and/or use our services, make use of our customer service or technical support then you may need to fill out a form requiring you to disclose your name and e-mail address. This information will be stored in our databases. This allows you to manage your user accounts and subscriptions in our online shop and make future purchases without having to re-enter your personal details each time.

3\. Cookies and Other Technologies

As is standard practice on many corporate websites, Y2Mate uses "cookies" and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. Y2Mate also uses cookies and other technologies to make sure that our online advertising is bringing customers to our products and services. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our website, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. And we use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes browser type, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We will not use the information collected to market directly to that person.

You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages.

4\. Securing the Transmission and Storage of Information

Y2Mate operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our users. Y2Mate takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or from the Website or Services. Your use of the Website and Services is at your own risk.

We treat the information you provide to us as confidential information; it is, accordingly, subject to our company's security procedures and corporate policies regarding protection and use of confidential information. After personally identifiable information reaches Y2Mate it is stored on a server with physical and electronic security features as customary in the industry, including utilization of login/password procedures and electronic firewalls designed to block unauthorized access from outside of Y2Mate. Because laws applicable to personal information vary by country, our offices or other business operations may put in place additional measures that vary depending on the applicable legal requirements. Information collected on the sites covered by this Privacy Policy is processed and stored in the United States and possibly other jurisdictions and also in other countries where Y2Mate and its service providers conduct business. All Y2Mate employees are aware of our privacy and security policies. Your information is only accessible to those employees who need it in order to perform their jobs.
